questionData = [
    {"text": "A slug's blood is green.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "The loudest animal is the African Elephant.", "answer": "False"},
    {"text": "Approximately one quarter of human bones are in the feet.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "The total surface area of a human lungs is the size of a football pitch.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "In West Virginia, USA, if you accidentally hit an animal with your car, you are free to take it home to eat.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "In London, UK, if you happen to die in the House of Parliament, you are entitled to a state funeral.", "answer": "False"},
    {"text": "It is illegal to pee in the Ocean in Portugal.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "You can lead a cow down stairs but not up stairs.", "answer": "False"},
    {"text": "Google was originally called 'Backrub'.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "Buzz Aldrin's mother's maiden name was 'Moon'.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "No piece of square dry paper can be folded in half more than 7 times.", "answer": "False"},
    {"text": "A few ounces of chocolate can to kill a small dog.", "answer": "True"}
]
question_data=[
    {
        "category":"Entertainment: Video Games",
        "type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy",
        "question":"The Indie Game Development Studio Cing, developers of Hotel     Dusk and Last Window, went bankrupt on March 1st, 2010.",
        "correct_answer":"True",
        "incorrect_answers":["False"]
    },
    {
        "category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Faust is a playable character in &quot;Guilty Gear Xrd Revelator&quot;.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
    {
        "category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Big the Cat is a playable character in &quot;Sonic Generations&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]
    },
    {
        "category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In &quot;Super Mario 3D World&quot;, the Double Cherry power-up originated from a developer accidentally making two characters controllable.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]
    },
    {
        "category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In Team Fortress 2, being disguised as a scout or medic results in a speed boost.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]
        },{
        "category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Rebecca Chambers does not appear in any Resident Evil except for the original Resident Evil and the Gamecube remake.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In &quot;Need for Speed: Porsche Unleashed&quot;, the player can only drive cars manufactured by Porsche.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{
        "category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"There are 2 player roles in Trouble in Terrorist Town.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{
        "category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In the Monster Hunter Series, it is possible to capture Elder Dragons.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{
        "category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"&quot;Resident Evil 7&quot; is the first first-person Resident Evil game.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]}]